

ABOUT ME

Front End Engineer passionate about Technologies, Rendering Performance, Security, Dev Tools, Browser Internals and User Experience.

I focus on Front-end/UI architecture, platform design, performance and building stellar experiences for customer delight using technical insights.

I love to write semantics code with modern styles for better interaction.

SKILLS

HTML5 CSS3

JavaScript

SCSS

Pug.js

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe Xd

SHIVAM GUPTA

web: imshivamgupta.github.io

email: shivamg8797@gmail.com

LinkedIn: imshivamgupta1

phone: +(91) 8090908320, 8979315982

EXPERIENCE

TERASOL TECHNOLOGIES/ FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Jan 2018 – Present

- Generating dynamic UI and Data provided by REST API in JSON Format.
- Maintained Client websites on an ongoing basis.
- Designed and Developed Custom WordPress Themes.
- Developing HTML5 pages such dashboards, scorecards and Graphs using JavaScript.
- Making Development plans, work flow and user test cases by providing input to client for good user experience.

CYBEROZE/ WEB DESIGNER

Jun 2017 – Aug 2017 (Intern)

- Designed and Developed views/template on top of Laravel using Blade template engine.
- Designed logos, banners and ads for client and company for Social Media Campaigns using Adobe Photoshop.

EDUCATION

DR. APJ ABDUL KALAM UNIVERSITY, LUCKNOW

2014-18

B. Tech in Computer Science and Engineering from Raj Kumar Goel Engineering College, Hapur (72.3%).

ACHIEVEMENT

GOOGLE INDIA CHALLENGE SCHOLARSHIP

Feb 2018

Front-End Web Developer Course from Udacity for Phase I.